<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://yusienia.github.io</id>
    <title>Sovereign Yusienia</title>
    <updated>2023-09-12T17:55:00.123Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://yusienia.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://yusienia.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>Sovereign Yusienia official website</subtitle>
    <logo>https://yusienia.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://yusienia.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2023, Sovereign Yusienia</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurora Twinkle attended the EU MicroCon in Ypres, Belgium]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/AHhHf6thE/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/AHhHf6thE/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-08-16T14:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The People's Revolutionary Repubulic of Yusienia was honored to participate in EU Microcon. The MicroCon is generally considered the most famous and important intermicronational conference. This EU MicroCon is the first MicroCon ever in Europe, and it is co-hosted by Flandrensis and Ladonia. It is hosted in Ypres, which located in the Flanders region of Belgium and has the world-famous Menin Gate.</p>
<p>On 10 August, President Aurora Twinkle fly from Athens to Bruselles, and visited this famous city, known as the capital of Europe.</p>
<p>The next day afternoon, Twinkle arrived in Ypres by train. She met with the leader of Coruscent and his family in a sushi restaurant. Coruscent is an Asian micronation and grabbed its name from Star Wars. Twinkle had dinner there, and together they meet with many micronational leaders: President Zar Antonov of Obscurium, Summi Imperatoria Christina of Cycoldia, and the delegation of Westarctica.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://yusienia.github.io/post-images/1694540257843.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://yusienia.github.io/post-images/1694540224068.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>Twinkle visited the Lille Gate and war cemetery with Coruscent leader family. Twinkle said, the visit to the war cemetery reminds her of the song &quot;It's a long way to Tipperary.&quot;</p>
<p>The attendees gathered together and attended The Last Post ceremony at Menin Gate. Then they meet and get a drink together.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://yusienia.github.io/post-images/1694540351182.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>In the morning of 12 August, the MicroCon started. Many attendees shared their amazing thoughts on the conference, and the representatives of the micronations showed their nations by their fascinating beautiful display tables.</p>
<p>Yusienia's display table shows QR codes to MicroWiki and Sovereign Yusienia, and have Yusienian badges, commemorative coins for this MicroCon, flags and some Yusienian ethnic food.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="4"><img src="https://yusienia.github.io/post-images/1694540089064.jpg" alt="Yusienia's display table" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>The MicroCon has established a communication platform for multilaterial meetings and provided a rare opportunity for leaders of various micronations to hold on bilaterial meetings. Twinkle met Prince Freï von Fräähsen, who came from a Nordic micronation, Lorenzburg, and was one of the speakers at the conference.Twinkle discussed about art and traditional Greek dance with him and they reached a consensus.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="5"><img src="https://yusienia.github.io/post-images/1694540332163.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>She also met and had cordinal and friendly conversations with several other micronational leaders and nobilities, like the Royal Family of Lithua, and the host of this conference, Grand Duke Nicholas of Flandrensis.</p>
<p>The Closing Ceremony annouce the end of this European Microcon, the diplomatic reception and dinner are followed.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="6"><img src="https://yusienia.github.io/post-images/1694540302557.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>Twinkle received 2 foreign honors: The Molossian Medal of Statesmanship, and the Obscurium Order of Friendship.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yusienia gets its fourth citizen]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/5tEkPMtBG/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/5tEkPMtBG/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-06-11T09:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On 4 June, Yusienia's population increased to four. The new citizen who joined Yusienia, named Xiran Jin, obtained Yusienia nationality and took an oath to become a full citizen of Yusienia. Aurora Twinkle presided over the ceremony. Afterwards, Twinkle hosted a barbeque banquet for the new citizen.<br>
Kostas, a Central Revolutionary Commissar, congratulated the new citizen on joining Yusienia.<br>
<img src="https://yusienia.github.io/post-images/1686494415407.jpg" alt="Twinkle and Xiran at the banquet" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National emblem made a change]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/ResvzcD37/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/ResvzcD37/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-05-29T14:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In recent days, the national emblem has undergone a change. The middle pattern of the new version of the national emblem is changed to a compass, a dip pen and a gear, representing science, art and industry respectively.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New National Anthem of Yusienia: Vamos Hijos de la Tierra Amada]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/ICeP9irWs/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/ICeP9irWs/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-02-27T09:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Vamos hijos de la Tierra Amada<br>
derrotamos al tirano<br>
Por la libertad nos espera,<br>
sin miedo a luchar y morir</p>
<p>De las montañas en la Balcaña<br>
a las olas del Egeo azul<br>
Yusienia libre y independente<br>
florece en asombrosa luz</p>
<p>[Refran x2]<br>
Avante, Compañeros!<br>
En lucha venceremos<br>
Cantemos: siempre viva<br>
Prosperidad y la paz</p>
<p>Salve patria tu hermosa bandera<br>
se compone de tres colores<br>
dorado, azul y verde selva<br>
Guíanos hacia futuro mejor</p>
<p>Sabia y Verona es heroica<br>
y Ladonia, Molossia, Obsidia,<br>
Yusienia con los pueblos gloriosos<br>
Sostenemos antorcha brillante!</p>
<p>[Refran x2]</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Her Serene Highness Aurora Twinkle's Statement about Urbo de Sophia]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/e9_4gqWrC/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/e9_4gqWrC/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-01-13T10:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>⚠️ This article have content related to sexual assault.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>We are aware of the situation involving with Sophia Swan, the dictator of the self-claimed &quot;micronation&quot; Urbo de Sophia, which had formal diplomatic relations with Yusienia, and now we no longer recognize its status as a sovereign state.</p>
<p>According to notices provided by a number of authoritative sources, Sophia sexual assaulted and abused many victims in recent years, he used the &quot;micronation&quot; claimed by himself, the &quot;Urbo de Sophia&quot;,  and the autism spectrum institution affiliated to his &quot;micronation&quot;, the &quot;AWM of Urbo de Sophia &quot;, as a cover to attract victims. This cannot be tolerated by the Yusienian government and the micronational community, when there is already definite evidence to prove his crime.</p>
<p>We established diplomatic relations by internet with &quot;Urbo de Sophia&quot; in late 2020 and early 2021 without our knowledge of these unrelated matters. There was nothing to do between our diplomatic relations with &quot;Urbo de Sophia&quot; and Sophia committing sex crimes. Institution &quot;AWM of Urbo de Sophia&quot; under &quot;Urbo de Sophia&quot; is totally not related to Yusienia.</p>
<p>We hope that the judiciary of the relevant country can give a fair judgment and uphold justice.</p>
<p>Aurora Twinkle<br>
Princess of Yusienia<br>
14 January 2023</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yusienia adopted new flags]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/VU0Fe6KpT/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/VU0Fe6KpT/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-10-16T04:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, Princess Aurora Twinkle decreed to change the country's civil flag and governmental flag.<br>
The new civil flag is a 2:1 solid green flag, and it is worth noting that this flag is almost identical to that of the former Great Socialist People's Libyan Arab Jamahiriya.<br>
The new government flag is the civil flag with the addition of a golden six-pointed mullet, which symbolizes the six principles of Hexasophy, Yusienia's basic philosophical theory.<br>
The princess expressed that a solid green flag wouldn't be very noticeable even when flying outdoors, but would look great in taffeta.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://yusienia.github.io/post-images/1665913237264.png" alt="The civil flag" loading="lazy"></figure>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://yusienia.github.io/post-images/1665913287306.png" alt="The governmental flag" loading="lazy"></figure>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sovereign Yusienia made a domain transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/leGoj21gZ/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/leGoj21gZ/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-10-15T23:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As you can see, the domain name of this website has been transferred to yusienia.github.io. This is the only domain name used to access this website.<br>
As an amateur browser side engineer and programmer, Princess Aurora Twinkle personally carried out the technical process of this domain name transfer. She changed both the organization name and repository name on Github. She also updated the website source code to make it more stable.<br>
Due to domain name transfer and other reasons, the website went down for a while on the morning of October 16, orloj time. If you cannot access Sovereign Yusienia with the new domain normally, please refresh your browser's cache.<br>
We apologize for the inconvenience caused to fellow compatriots and international friends.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Princess talked about the re-establishment of the National Assembly, and a new political party has emerged]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/P1TmYYDbR/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/P1TmYYDbR/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-10-11T08:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On 8 October 2022, Her Serene Highness Aurora Twinkle made an announcement on de-facto Yusienian official discord server:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>For the latest political reform, I hereby form the Yusienian Justice Party.<br>
The list of the first National Assembly will be announced later.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This meant that the National Assembly was re-established. Although the Princess did not release the list after the announcement.</p>
<p>The princess said she is going to rename the Justice Party to the Constitutional Party because she is still inclined to make a constitution and that the party's name would be abbreviated in Greek as &quot;SYKO&quot;, which means fig in Greek.</p>
<p>Also, the princess proposed a new government flag design on the evening of 11 October, a golden hexagram on a green field.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the princess said she is suffering from gender dysphoria recently. She said she should try her best to be feminine, at least grow her hair. She kindly requests people of the world give their support and blessings to her.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yusienia adopted new national anthem "Oh Yusienia, land beloved and graceful", and the old anthem will become official traditional anthem]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/vuFNvcIpP/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/vuFNvcIpP/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-07-07T22:18:09.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>At the beginning of July, Her Serene Highness the Princess announced Yusienia will have a new national anthem, which takes the tune of the Bashkortostan national anthem, and the lyrics are also taken from the unofficial English lyrics of the Bashkortostan national anthem, with some changes.</p>
<p>The princess said that the reason for changing the official national anthem is that now the most commonly used language in Yusienia is English, and it is inappropriate to continue to use the Chinese national anthem. But the old national anthem still has rich historical significance for Yusienia, so it will become the official traditional national anthem and will be used in some ceremonies.</p>
<h3 id="oh-yusienia-land-beloved-and-graceful">Oh Yusienia, land beloved and graceful</h3>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh, Yusienia, land beloved and graceful,<br>
Thou rich cradle of folks bountiful.<br>
From the Ionia ancient and beautiful,<br>
To this land natal and wonderful.</p>
<p>Glory to Yusienian land!<br>
Blessed be this land elegant and divine.<br>
With the world we are together as one,<br>
Blossom ye, Yusienian land!</p>
<p>Oh, Yusienia, thou dawn's shining light,<br>
Thou bring'st us to good will and delight.<br>
Like a fine rainbow thou shinest bright,<br>
May thy destined victory be in sight.</p>
<p>Glory to Yusienian land!<br>
Blessed be this land elegant and divine.<br>
With the world we are together as one,<br>
Blossom ye, Yusienian land!</p>
<p>Oh Yusienia, thou'st traversed arduous paths,<br>
Through defeat we've overcome thy hardships.<br>
Thy destiny awaiteth all of us,<br>
Wave thy banner we proud and glorious.</p>
<p>Glory to Yusienian land!<br>
Blessed be this land elegant and divine.<br>
With the world we are together as one,<br>
Blossom ye, Yusienian land!</p>
<p>My republic, shine like a beautiful star,<br>
Thou rejoicest in happy success.<br>
In this land we shall with honour progress,<br>
We chant thee thine anthem harmonious.</p>
<p>Glory to Yusienian land!<br>
Blessed be this land elegant and divine.<br>
With the world we are together as one,<br>
Blossom ye, Yusienian land!</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My personal life trivia and future goals for Yusienia]]></title>
        <id>https://yusienia.github.io/post/nSLmUNsPz/</id>
        <link href="https://yusienia.github.io/post/nSLmUNsPz/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-06-24T13:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Sorry for this chaotic title.<br>
It seems like I've kind of wanted to make this site my personal website lately. That's not bad - it fits a country with a personal dictatorship. I'm going to write something here in the first person.<br>
I thought a lot about my name, and I settled on one: Aurora Twinkle. It's a feminine name that can be written entirely in the pure Latin alphabet without diacritics, and is also easy to pronounce and easy to remember. I might try this name for a while and then make it my official name.<br>
The domain of this site will change, that's for sure. I will rename the organization on github to Yusienia, so the domain will become yusienia.github.io.<br>
You probably already know that I have elected the Prime Minister of the Republic of Caelesta. Thank you to the citizens of Caelesta who supported me in the election. I will come up with some of my own guidelines, plans, policies. I'm still the only one in the Democratic Conservative Party, but the other parties seem to be too.. Some are not active anymore, like the left-wing UWU. At least the DCP has gone from opposition to ruling party.<br>
There's not much that can be done in Caelesta's parliament -- I mean, I don't dare to presume my usual petty bills when the president hasn't proposed anything. Aside from politics, I'm still writing poetry and drawing, drawing microball comics or something, although my creations are sparse.<br>
June is the fastest month in my opinion. I didn't go to other European countries, I don't have enough money to go to the micro euro summit, which will be held in Prague. And the another reason is that no one is going with me, a lonely princess without maids and knights around her sounds bad, doesn't it? I also didn't go to the International Congress of Vexillology, although I thought I could. I also think that I need to prepare more for such an event. Maybe in a few years I will be at Microcon.<br>
I'll do a better statistic on Yusienia's population. Then I'll reorganize our partnership. None of this is complicated work. I have some complicated plans, these are holding cultural weeks, making new flags and orders, etc. I'll probably be able to get my hands on those beautiful beads soon. that's all.</p>
<p>Princess Aurora Twinkle (yeah I started my new name here.)</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>